OK, so let's go over to the C file.
We're going to include.
ESP HGTV server tonnage.
And that's for HTP server component.
And we can also include ESP luggage.
And we'll also include here, HDP server Dot H.
And include.
Tasks common.
And also include Wi-Fi app Dunwich.
And now let's add a tag used for ESP serial console messages.
And stay static const char tag.
And call it HGTV server.
OK, now we'll create a CTP server test handle.
And it'll be static, it's handled, underscored T.
And call it HTP server handle and set it to No.
And this is the HGTV server instance, and that will need to use will be called various functions from
the API, such as HPD Start and Stop.
And when we register, you are eye handlers using the HPD register, you are a handler function.
OK, so now let's take care of the embedded files.
Which includes Jake Query.
Index HTML.
APT casts and apt J.S..
Andy Favicon, Iko Files.
OK, so now we need to externe Konst undated type.
And notice how the files seem to be typed here, so we'll say a query underscore and just follow me
here.
For the start.
And then use Asymm and then quotes.
And just follow me the rest of the way.
And just paste the rest of the name here.
And that's how we handle the start.
So now just copy it.
And then paste it here and change this to end.
And the entiere.
The next let's just do the same for index studies HTML.
And that's for the start.
And then do the same like before.
So now just copy that and paste it.
Let's do the end.
And then let's do the ABC East start here.
And then they'll do the end portion.
OK, so now let's do the start for us.
Then now let's do the end for the US.
And then do the last one.
For favicon, Iko Stoat.
OK, and then we'll also do favicon could end.
OK, that looks good.
So now we can head over to the head of file.
And then just grab our start and stop prototypes for now.
And then our first, we can go to a CTP server start.
And let's grab the HGTV server handle and say, if it should be server handle is no.
Then will say a CTP server handle equals the result of HGTV server configured.
And dysfunction will need to create later.
So for now, let's go over to the HGTV service.
Stop.
And say, if HGTV server handle meaning that the HGTV server has been initialized already.
Then we'll call HTP stop.
And insert the handle parameter.
And now ESP log information.
HGTV servers stop.
Colon stopping HGTV server.
And then we can set the HGTV server handle back to No.
OK, that looks good.
Now, let's create the HGTV server configured function and come here and say sets up the default.
HPD server configuration.
And returns HGTV server instance handle.
If successful.
NULL.
Otherwise.
So we'll say static httpd handle underscored T.
And it's the HGTV server, configure function, and it's void.
And now will generate the default configuration.
So here we'll need an instance of the handle HPT config type, and we'll call it config.
Equals eight httpd default config function.
And here are right to do.
That we should create should be server and monitored task.
So we'll do that later.
And then also write another to do to create the message queue.
And now we can specify the core that the HTP server will run on.
And for that sake, config that Core ID.
Equals our GDP server.
Task Corps.
And next will adjust the default priority.
To one less than the Wi-Fi application desk.
And do conflict task priority.
Equals HGTV server task priority.
And now we'll bump up the stack size.
Because the default is four thousand ninety six bytes, so we'll do config Typekit stack size.
Equals our HTTP server task stack size.
And next will increase our you are right handlers.
Which is the maximum amount of you are right handlers.
In, say, conflict.
Max, you are right, handlers.
And Tony should be good enough.
All right.
And now we'll increase the time out limits.
And do Config Dutt receive.
Wait time out.
As 10 seconds.
And the next to conflict sent wait time out as 10 seconds as well.
All right.
And now let's log the configured information.
And for the message, we'll say HTP conserver can figure.
Starting server on port.
And we'll print the port, No.
And then we'll say with task priority.
And we'll give the priority here.
All right, and then we'll get the config that server port.
And the conflict task priority.
OK, so we'll see this information on the terminal monitor when the Web server starts next, let's start
the httpd server and we'll say if they start.
With the reference to the HTP server handle.
In a reference to the config.
And if it returns, ESP, OK.
Then we want to ESP log information.
That the HGTV server can figure.
Is now registering the Yura handlers.
And then first, we'll say, registered the J Query handler.
And Hugh, we need to speed you are a struct.
And call it Jake Weary underscored us.
And let's set the you are right.
As forward slash and the file name here.
And the next will specify the method.
As an HTP get.
And now we need to provide a handler.
And give it a function name as HGTV server.
Jake Weary, Handler.
And now let's set this user underscores CTCs.
As no.
All right, so that looks good, so now we can register that you are a handler using the ftpd, register
your eye handler.
And then we'll pass the 8TB server handle.
And a reference to the J Query underscored a structure.
OK, cool.
So now let's copy this one.
And then paste it down.
So we can register the index HTML handler.
And now change this name here to index underscore HTML.
And the are.
It's just a forward slash.
Then now let's update the handler name like so.
And also copy and paste.
To register the index CMLL handler and now just copy and paste.
To the next, you are a handler.
And change the name to that success handler.
And then update the name here.
And then update your.
And now we can update the handle of function name.
And then registered the app on Underscores CIUSSS Handler.
So now let's do the Duchess.
And then change it to A.j.'s.
And then update the rest of the same way.
OK, good, so now let's register the favicon, Dutt Iko.
And then we'll update it like so.
Now we can return the server handle.
OK.
And outside this if block.
We can return now.
Right here, great.
So next will define the you or I handlers, but I think now is a good time to take a short break and
we'll regroup in the next one.